

Contact

Phone

0942274558

Email

vothanhtien190901@gmail.com

Address

48 Cao Thang, Da Nang

Education

09/2019 - Present

University of Technology and Education - University of Danang

Hobbies

Sport: Football, e-sport

VO THANH TIEN

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Overview

With experience studying at University of Technical Education - University of Danang, majoring in Information Technology, i am very much looking forward to becoming a Front-End Developer. Having a solid knowledge of HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, REACTJS(Next js) and other skills that i hone daily. In the next year, I want tobecome a full-fledged developer on the way to workand accompany thecompany which can help me develop myself as well as contribute a lot tothe development of the company.

Work Experience

11/2022 - 01/2023

Safehorizons Software Service One Member Co., Ltd **Front-end Developer**

Internship

(09/2022 - 10/2022)

Team member, Project Book-store website

- Build UI for website by React js/ Redux, Html, Css, Tailwind, Axios
- Solution architect
- Link github: GitHub TIEN1909/book-store

(11/12/2022 - 13/12/2022)

Myself, Project movie website

- Build UI for website by Next js, Next-auth, Tailwind, Html, Css, Formik, Axios
- Solution architect
- Link github: GitHub TIEN1909/watch-me

SKILL

Main:

- Html, Css (Sass), Tailwind, Javascript
- React js (Next js), Redux, RESTful API
- Git, Responsive

Other:

- PHP (Basic), MySQL
- Photoshop, Figma, Adobe XD
- Exchange, Listening, Adaptability, Teamwork.